simplecdn.net 2011-01-06

# News | SimpleCDN Privacy Policy | www.SimpleCDN.com

Privacy Policy Welcome to the SimpleCDN Technologies ("SimpleCDN") web site (www.simplecdn.com), and any other web sites, networks, applications, or services operated or produced by SimpleCDN (collectively, the "SimpleCDN Platform"). SimpleCDN values the privacy of the users, subscribers, publishers, members, and others who visit and use the SimpleCDN Platform (collectively or individually, "you" or "Users"). 

By using the SimpleCDN Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not use the SimpleCDN Platform. 

This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with the SimpleCDN Acceptable Use Policy at http://www.simplecdn.com/news/termsofuse. Your use of the SimpleCDN Platform and any personal information you provide through the SimpleCDN Platform are subject at all time to this Privacy Policy and the Acceptable Use Policy. 

TABLE OF CONTENTS 

  1. The Information SimpleCDN Collects 
  2. The Way SimpleCDN Uses Information 
  3. When SimpleCDN Discloses Information 
  4. Your Choices 
  5. Web Beacons 
  6. Data Security 
  7. Children's Privacy 
  8. International Visitors 
  9. In the Event of Merger or Sale 
  10. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy 
  11. Effective Date, Date Last Modified 
  12. Unsolicited E-mails 
  13. SimpleCDN Contact Information 

1\. The Information SimpleCDN Collects: 

• User–provided Information: You may provide to SimpleCDN what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, credit card number and billing information) if you upload, purchase, or download certain content or products from the SimpleCDN Platform, enter contests or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the SimpleCDN Platform. You may also provide to SimpleCDN demographic information; information related to your web site such as the name, description and primary language of the site; and company name, telephone number, e–mail address, mailing address, and personal contacts within your company. 

SimpleCDN also provides an area for people looking for a job at SimpleCDN Technologies. In applying for a job or asking for information about a job we may require personal information from you such as your address or e–mail address. 

• "Cookies" Information: When you access the SimpleCDN Platform, we may send one or more cookies – small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer. SimpleCDN may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the SimpleCDN Platform. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SimpleCDN only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

• "Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the SimpleCDN Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug–ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, JavaScript enablement, the content and pages that you access on the SimpleCDN Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the SimpleCDN Platform, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages. 

2\. The Way SimpleCDN Uses Information: 

• SimpleCDN uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the SimpleCDN Platform, to allow us to charge and invoice you, as well as to track user–generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. 

• We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major SimpleCDN Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the SimpleCDN Platform. 

• SimpleCDN uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the SimpleCDN Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

• SimpleCDN may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to: (a) automatically update the SimpleCDN application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re–enter it during your visit or the next time you access the SimpleCDN Platform; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. 

• Information submitted to SimpleCDN as part of applications for employment or for partner candidates is used by SimpleCDN to evaluate your qualifications for the positions sought. 

3\. When SimpleCDN Discloses Information: 

• SimpleCDN does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the SimpleCDN Platform becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. 

• We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; validate credit card numbers; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist SimpleCDN in improving the SimpleCDN Platform and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. • SimpleCDN may share aggregate statistical information gathered from you and other Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a web site or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out registration forms. We share such information only on an aggregate and anonymous basis. 

• SimpleCDN may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good–faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity. 

• SimpleCDN also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect SimpleCDN from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third–party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the SimpleCDN Platform; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of SimpleCDN, our Users, or others. 

4\. Your Choices: 

You may, of course, decline to share your personally–identifiable information with SimpleCDN, in which case SimpleCDN will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the SimpleCDN Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences by sending us a request at: support@simplecdn.com. 

You do not need to set up a user id and password to use our web sites because we do not require you to establish your identity when you visit our sites. However, if you have subscribed for some of our services or are a customer seeking access to your account information, you will have to provide passwords. We recommend you do not divulge your password to anyone. SimpleCDN will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e–mail. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. 

5\. Web Beacons

Our web pages contain electronic image requests (called a "single–pixel gif" or "web beacon" request) that allow us to count page views and to access cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically 1–by–1 pixel files, but their presence can usually be seen within a browser by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." We also include web beacons in HTML–formatted newsletters that we send to opt–in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. SimpleCDN web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personally identifiable information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile anonymous information about web site usage. 

6\. Our Commitment to Data Security: 

SimpleCDN uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to SimpleCDN, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, SimpleCDN makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If SimpleCDN learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. SimpleCDN may post a notice on the SimpleCDN Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at: support@simplecdn.com. 

7\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SIMPLECDN PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, SimpleCDN does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years–of–age. If SimpleCDN learns that personally–identifiable information of persons less than 13–years–of–age has been collected on or through the SimpleCDN Platform, then SimpleCDN will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the SimpleCDN Platform, then please contact SimpleCDN at support@simplecdn.com to have that child's information deleted. 

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your childrens' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While SimpleCDN does not endorse these resources, we provide information about them as a public service to our community. 

• "OnGuard Online," maintained by the Federal Trade Commission. • WiredSafety • Netsmartz.org • The Child Safety Network • Control Kids • Cyber Sitter • Net Nanny

8\. International Visitors: 

For Users visiting the SimpleCDN Platform from the European Economic Area or other non–U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the SimpleCDN Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non–U.S. territory for use by SimpleCDN and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because SimpleCDN operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the SimpleCDN Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries. 

9\. In the Event of Merger or Sale: 

In the event that SimpleCDN is acquired by or merged with a third–party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

10\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy: 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the SimpleCDN Platform constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage) and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information. 

11\. Effective Date, Date Last Modified: 

Privacy Policy effective as of September 1, 2007. 

Privacy Policy last modified on September 1, 2007. 

12\. Unsolicited E–mails

SimpleCDN does not send unsolicited e–mails to non–public addresses or to anyone who has asked us not to contact him or her. Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have subscribed to them. To stop receiving e–mails or newsletters from SimpleCDN, either click on an unsubscribe link on the e–mail or newsletter itself or send a request to be unsubscribed to support@simplecdn.com . 

13\. SimpleCDN Contact Information: 

Please contact SimpleCDN with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third–party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: support@simplecdn.com. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
